I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even
you can't navigate If someone
strong like you is lost then
who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart exists.
It's been your kindness and your strength!
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that!
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can!
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all?
Well, we're dashing together.
No, we're never gonna fall, you know!
The whole world may now be my enemy.
What a swirl, but I ain't
backing down so long as I'm free!
Thought I'll give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go!
A short time ago, before
Luffy's departure,
he made a visit to the
ruins of Odin Castle,
where the graves of Kozuki
Odin and his allies once were.
However, thanks to Kaido's blast breath,
there was nothing left but destruction.
Years ago, Odin built his first castle
there when he became the Daimyo of Kuri.
I'm the Daimyo!
Luffy!
Hi!
Hello there, Luffy Toto. Hey, guys.
What's going on?
Why are all of you here?
We came to tell Lord Odin
that we won the battle.
It's been rather eventful since we've
been away, so there's much to discuss.
Bigger question is,
why are you Karoo here?
To see Odin, same as you.
You two would have been
good friends, I'm certain.
He would be honored to meet the man
who saved his country from Kaido!
You think so?
Lord Odin, thanks to Sir
Lufitaro and his friends.
We defeated Orochi and Kaido.
At long last, the land of Wano is free.
As for Lord Momonosuke, he
has become a beloved shogun.
With us beside him, he will make this
country a land of peace as it was before.
Your people will smile again.
I only wish that Ashura
and Iza were here too.
They'll always be here.
For we will carry them in our hearts.
Just as we do with Lord Oden.
Oh, well spoken.
I'm sure they're having their own banquet,
and they'll feast again when we join them.
I'm not going to keel over yet,
but I can't wait to have
our lord's ode in when I do.
I haven't forgotten the flavor.
And how could I?
It's the flavor of our friendship.
It tasted even better after training.
We ate and ate.
That sounds nice.
Wish I could try some, too.
Yeah, me too.
If you guys know the recipe, we
can have Sanji cook up a pot.
We should stock up on some
ingredients to take on the Sunny.
Yeah, go for it.
And get as much as you can carry.
Sir Luffy.
Will you be leaving soon?
Yeah.
With all our hearts, once
again, we must thank you.
We owe you our lives.
Cut that out!
We're friends, aren't we? Huh?
Huh?
What's up, Carrot?
You, Chia, can't go!
My heart can't take it!
I want to stay with you, Chia!
It's not fair, Nami!
Carrot? What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Because this is goodbye.
I'm going back to Zou.
I have to protect my homeland
with Wanda and the others.
Miyagi, Tristan, thank you for
all your help. My pleasure.
Thank you, Karoo, for teaching me
so much as a doctor and as a friend.
Please don't work too hard.
Get good sleep.
Aw, I'm reminded of the first time we met.
As I recall, Carrot, you
stowed away on the sunny.
Seems your dream to see the
ocean came true in a big way.
Was it all you hoped for?
It was all of that and more!
I saw crazy islands and went on big
adventures and made amazing friends!
It was scary sometimes, too.
But I think I came out of it
a lot stronger than before.
I owe it all to you, Tia. So thanks!
I'll treasure these memories
for the rest of my life!
There's only one last thing
for us to do. Got you!
I had so much fun spending
time with you, Tia-nami.
My Beast.
I miss you.
I didn't forget my children.
That tickled carrot.
I'm so glad I got to be your bro.
Oh, yeah.
When I was coming out here, I
saw Zoro. Yeah? Where was he?
20 minutes.
3 minutes.
2 minutes. 2
minutes.
Let's share a drink.
What are you doing here?
Having a few drinks with
your old man, that's all.
I'll pour one for you!
Thanks.
Did you put these flowers here?
Huh?
Uh-huh
Big sis helped me out.
It was her idea?
Zoro Giri, you came to pay
your respects as well? Yeah.
May you rest in peace, Lord Yasui.
They'll build you a nice
temple soon, promise.
Then I'll come and visit
you all the time, okay?
You'll never be lonely with
me around, Dad. Right? Right!
It seems you came here to say farewell.
Does that mean you'll be leaving?
That the time has come?
Yeah.
I will certainly miss you.
Not only you, I will also have to bid
farewell to my father's beloved Enma.
I suppose so.
You can't have it back.
No, of course not.
He still holds a grip on the blade
that slices through the deepest hells.
Odin was one hell of a swordsman.
This sword is a beast.
It would take a true master to tame it.
It sounds like you're being modest.
You saved the land of Wano by
wielding that sword yourself.
You're a master just like my father was.
No.
I'm still not good enough.
Don't say that.
It looks to me like Enma is rejoicing.
It's pleased to have a partner like you.
Now get stronger.
Just watch me, Enma.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You trying to pull one over
on me, you cheeky brat?
What was that, boss?
Don't tell me there's something
wrong with my repair work.
You're damn right there is.
Wanna fight?
Or do you need to get your eyes
checked, you useless old fart bag?
You're the one who asked me to double
check your repairs, you cocky little turd.
Don't start pissing on me because I did you
a favor, even if it was a waste of time.
Everything's perfect.
But you knew that already.
You little punk.
Come on.
You kind of left me a
spot to fix as a courtesy.
See?
I climbed up here just
to look like a fool.
Sorry you can't handle
my super repair work.
You're the shipwright
of the crew, aren't you?
The Straw Hats wouldn't have made
it this far if you weren't a pro.
So long, you damn oversized blockhead.
I gotta miss your big fat mouth.
I'll miss you.
Is everything OK back there?
My apologies, sir. One
moment. I'm on my way.
Here, thank you for your patience.
No prop.
Now, regarding your color, it's blue.
Trust me, you'll look great!
Usuhachi, you're so cool!
He's the most handsome man in all of Wano!
Show me a smile.
Of course, young madam,
anything for a fan!
Oh yeah!
Hey, wait, that's not what I need?
Aha, you want a little more flair!
Well, I've got just the thing!
I know you'll turn some heads with this!
He's so Head!
Hey, Lady Killer!
I've never seen anyone
wear that color so well!
He's red hot!
Hmm...
Be careful not to fall in love with me.
Wait a minute, stop distracting me!
Huh?
I just need plain black fabric.
Nothing fancy!
I'm gonna need lots and lots though, okay?
But that's so terribly plain, sir!
A gentleman like you deserves much more!
Thanks, but it's not like that!
Don't tell anyone, but...
What?
I didn't know, sir!
I shall provide you with the
finest that Wano has to offer!
Nice! Thanks, buddy!
Good!
I think that's enough for today!
Thank you for the lesson!
Sanguro's special Sabo is here!
Delicious.
I can never get enough of this.
Perfect as always.
Thank you.
So, what do you think?
It's amazing.
That's what I like to hear.
Oh, hey, Chouchou.
How's it going, pal?
Here, you want a pet?
What a cutie.
You like that, huh?
What's up? You good?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just realized I never thanked
you for everything you did for me.
You saved my life at Onigashima.
Don't mention it. Okay.
It was my pleasure to help you.
Will you sell me your Sabo tomorrow too?
And the next day and the day after that.
I feel like it gives me
the power to do my best.
You really know how to
flatter a guy, don't you?
But I'm afraid I'm leaving soon.
Already?
But I...
Excuse me.
Yes?
I don't suppose you could
spare a bowl for me.
Anytime, Robin.
Thanks for stopping by.
And make it a hot one,
if you would, please.
Yes, ma 'am. Coming right up.
And can I have one, too?
Yeah, fine. Hey!
You're working so hard.
Here, I brought you a little snack.
I think you've all earned a break.
You're the best. Thanks
a bunch. Looks good.
Don't mind if I do.
That smells great.
And it tastes even better, I bet.
Sorry for the wait.
I've been so busy. I
understand. It's okay.
Bet it'll be worth the wait.
It sure was.
I'm grateful for the food.
Your red bean soup's the best
thing in the world, Otsudu?
Remember, there's rice cakes too!
Mmm, love how it's so soft and chewy.
Eat up, you can have as
many bowls as you want.
Tama, what's the matter?
Even though I'm having fun, I
remembered you're gonna leave soon.
And then, I got a lump in my throat.
First Ace, then you, all
the people I love, leave.
And after what happened to Ace, I'm
afraid I'll never see you again.
Don't worry.
You gave me rice when you
barely had any for yourself.
We're friends.
I could never forget you.
Me too.
I won't forget you either.
You'll all be in my heart
no matter where you go.
That's right.
Train hard while I'm gone. I will.
Someday, we'll meet again.
Thank you!
Thank you so much, big friend!
I'll get real strong! You'll see!
I'll be a hero like you and Abe someday!
And now, we return to the present.
Hey, Luffy!
We can set sail whenever you're ready!
Alright.
But are you really sure you
want to leave like this?
We didn't say goodbye
to Momo or to Kinamon.
Seems kind of wrong after all
we've been through with them.
She's right, as always.
They'll be fine.
If Luffy wants to go, let's go.
Why you gotta be such a bastard, Mosshead?
Screw off, curly brows. Hey! What?
Although,
it is a bit of a shame since
we shared so many adventures
with those two even before
we came to the land of Wano.
It does feel a bit cold to
silently sail away like this.
Well, Luffy, you can make the call.
Don't worry, guys.
He'll be here soon.